https://staufferdiesel.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for StaufferDiesel.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only collect information such as your name, email address and phone number when you choose to submit it to us via one of our online forms.
We may use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party other than as necessary to fulfill your request. In the event that there is a local Stauffer Diesel dealer or distributor in your area, we may provide them with your information so that they may follow up with you.
We may contact you in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. If we contact you and you do not want to hear from us again, let us know via phone, email or by unsubscribing through the link provided in our email communication.
We collect aggregate information on how our website is used by visitors. This information is not associated with any personally identifying information unless you have chosen to identify yourself by submitting one of our online forms or by clicking on one of our email communications.
We will never sell or rent any of the information we collect to any third party.
Security
We do not collect sensitive information such as social security numbers or credit card numbers through our website. If you choose to submit your name, email address or other information using one of our online forms you do so at your own risk.
Cookies
We use “cookies” on this website. A cookie is a piece of data stored in a site visitor’s browser to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. We may also use cookies to show targeted advertisements.
Some of our business partners may use also cookies on our site (for example, Google). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
You may disable cookies at any time using your browser’s privacy settings.
Sharing
We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers, such as Google. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email.
Contact
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us directly using the information below.
Stauffer Diesel
34 Stauffer Lane
Ephrata, PA 17522
Ph: (717) 738-2500
Ready to Learn More?
Call: 717.738.2500
Contact Us
Diesel Engine Parts & Accessories
Deutz Oil & FluidsDeutz Lift PumpsDeutz BeltsDeutz AlternatorsDeutz StartersDeutz Air FiltersDeutz Fuel FiltersDeutz Oil FiltersMiscellaneous
Having trouble finding a part?Call our parts department for assistance
Ready to Learn More?
717.738.2500
Contact Us
